Provided by Phat Huu
Modify by Blue-Bird™
Min-jeong, this way.
This way.
You bastards!
24 hours ago
Hurry. Put them in the bag.
What the hell?
- What the hell?
- What is that?
Get off me!
Fucking cat!
What are you doing?
We don't have time. Hurry!
Wang-yi!
What are you doing?
What are you doing over there?
What's going on?
Wang-yi.
Wang-yi!
From Wuhan, China,
on 2019 December 8,
a case of pneumonia by unknown
cause was found
JNC MEDIA GROUP presents
a LEE FILM production
" GANGNAM ZOMBIE "
This year's Christmas doesn't
seem as jolly as last year's.
This is because although
it's been almost two years
since the first confirmed case
of COVID-19,
we cannot be relieved
of the disease yet.
What's your take on this, Professor?
We have realized
how powerful this virus is
while experiencing multiple
mass infections.
By witnessing the spread
of the disease even in summer,
we have concluded that
this is the virus
we have never experienced before.
Yes.
Do you think the current
situation will continue
unless the medicine is developed?
Yes, I do.
Let's get to work.
On top of everything, even after
COVID-19, unexpected mutant virus
will keep disrupting humankind.
The life of humankind will be
divided into pre and post COVID-19.
I am concerned if we can survive
in the case
of appearance of another virus.
The era
of "With COVID-19" has begun.
Still, we should enjoy Christmas.
Good.
This stop is Gangnam-gu
Office Station.
The next stop is Cheongdam-dong
Raemian Apartment.
Isn't he crazy?
He must be nuts.
What's he doing?
What the hell.
Somebody call the police!
What is he eating?
He is eating raw meat!
Out of the way, please!
This way!
Check this guy out.
He barged into my shop
and started eating raw meat.
Do something.
What's his deal?
Oh, no.
Sir.
What the...
Hey, you!
Put that down and come with us
to the police office.
Oh! What's happening?
The suspect is on the loose.
I need a backup.
- Get him!
Hi, mom.
Come back to your hometown
so you can grow oriental melons
with me.
Stop wasting your time in Seoul.
I am worried about
this COVID-19 thing.
Mom,
other moms are all over their kids
telling them to get a job in Seoul.
Why do you keep telling me
to leave Seoul?
How nice would it be if
we could farm together?
Whatever. I have got plenty
of things to do here.
What is it? Do you have
a girlfriend or something?
Jeez, mom!
Do you live with her?
It's not like that.
Living here gives me...
Hey!
What the...
My phone's broken. What are
you going to do about this?
I am talking to you!
- Let go of me.
- I said, stop!
Stop it already!
Min-jeong?
Hey...
Where did he go?
What the hell.
We were just talking.
Why do you butt in?
What's your deal?
You guys spiked her drink,
didn't you?
She doesn't get like this no matter
how much she drinks.
Did you drug them?
You violated special law
on sexually violent crimes.
This madam just sobered me right up.
Hey.
Are you a prosecutor?
Are you a lawyer?
Dude, madam is too much.
You went too far.
Who the hell are you?
Get lost.
It's too early in the morning
for all this hassle.
Why don't we get on our ways now?
Let's go.
What the fuck?
Do you know who we are?
I can take this once.
I can take this one hit.
That's okay. I understand.
It's okay. Let's just smile.
Let's go our separate ways now.
You little shit!
You bastard!
Let go of me.
Mother fucker!
I just lowered my guard.
You stay there!
I will come back for you!
Losers.
Min-jeong, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Let's just go.
Min-jeong!
Are you really okay?
Shall I call the police
and put them behind bars?
- Hyun-seok.
- Yes.
Can you beat those two-bit thugs?
Hey, you just saw what happened.
I can take them in my sleep.
No, I mean by law.
If they get hot-shot lawyers,
you will be
the one ending up in jail.
Why didn't you get contact numbers
of those two ladies, then?
Will you take responsibility for
them if their personal information
is disclosed?
Not really...
It's just that
you don't look too good.
But still,
didn't you find me kind of cool?
A little bit.
Wait for me, Min-jeong!
What are you doing after work?
It's Christmas Eve today.
So what, it's Christmas Eve?
I will just go home and sleep.
If you don't have any plans, do you
want to go to a concert with me?
I have got tickets.
I am not interested.
Go with someone else.
No pressure.
I know we are just colleagues.
Min-jeong! It will be fun...
Hold it!
The sixth floor?
The YouTuber?
Yes. Why ask if you already know?
Let's see.
You are three months late
on your rent.
It's not only the rent. I haven't
been paid for three months.
I don't care about your wage.
Is there a problem?
Why can't you pay your rent
for three months?
Right?
I think you need to ask
my boss about that.
Your boss keeps ignoring my calls.
I think he is avoiding me.
Go tell your boss.
If he doesn't pay
the three-months worth
of rent until the end of this month,
he will have to clear out.
Understood?
My day is just getting better
and better.
- What?
- Nothing.
I will tell him.
Wait.
You know you are not allowed to
smoke in the office, don't you?
I don't smoke.
It's the poor ones
who have no manner.
If you don't get their rent
in three days,
I will deduct it from your wages.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
That bastard.
Min-jeong!
Dae-yeong!
Okay, today's special!
'What happens when a zombie attacks
a backup national athlete
in Taekwondo?'
What did you think, guys?
Our Taekwondo Boy, Lee Hyun-seok
just slayed the zombie.
I guess his body just had
a knee-jerk reaction.
What was it like for you, Hyun-seok?
Knock it off already, boss.
We will come back
with more fun content.
Bye, guys!
Cut! Good job, man!
Thanks to you, this Christmas
eve will be unforgettable.
Did you think I had let you know
I was going to film you
for a prank video?
Hi, Min-jeong. Just leave him there.
You, take care of the zombie.
We have ourselves an awesome clip.
Shall we go and edit the shit out
of the clip?
Let's go.
Dae-yeong.
I didn't kick you that hard.
Get up.
I said get up!
Call 911!
What do you mean by 911?
Blood...
My nose is bleeding.
I will treat you to BBQ.
- I will treat you to BBQ.
- Korean BBQ?
High-quality Korean beef?
Sure. Just get in the office now.
Wait for me.
Cut! Okay!
That's it.
Jeez.
You are awesome at editing,
Min-jeong.
Hyun-seok's reaction is a bit short.
Is that so?
This is all about the reaction
of a person whose being pranked.
In that case...
Yes, there.
Put a slow motion there.
Just like that.
That's it.
Our princess is
in a sticky situation.
Aren't you gonna help her,
Taekwondo Boy?
Follow me, Dae-yeong.
What is it?
Boss.
Jeez.
What is it?
Dae-yeong wants to have a meeting.
A meeting?
About what, piggy?
It's about...
I wonder what it's about.
I suggested the ways
to improve our channel.
Yes,
the ways to improve our channel.
That's right.
Yes?
I am so proud of you.
Hey.
You have been working hard behind
my back.
Sure.
Let's have a meeting.
Kangnam Family There have been 3,
237 subscribers
for our YouTube channel,
for the past three months.
7, 200 views
for the most watched video
and 2, 300 views was the least.
At this rate,
when will we get the Silver Button?
And when will we get
the Gold Button?
The last month's revenue
was 230,000 won.
We worked our asses off.
And all we get is 230,000 won?
That's...
Landlady
Come on.
Right on time, landlady.
Look.
Let's stop rubbing our wounds
with salt.
What can we do to save our channel?
We need to focus on
and clarify our content.
We have been creating content only
on what you want to do.
We need to create contents that
actually will engage the viewers.
I have got a great idea.
You see,
I used to be a member of a boy band.
X-factor! TJ!
You used to be in a boy band?
- It was 20 years ago.
- Oh, really?
You two are killing me.
Screw you!
Jeez.
Landlady I am working hard
to pay you the rent!
Boss.
When are we getting paid?
I have got rent to pay too.
Exactly.
Let's do our best,
to skyrocket the hell out of it.
That way, I will be able
to give you the wage too.
or I could fire your asses!
Hmm.
Boss.
What is it now?
You can't smoke in here.
You really aren't on my side,
are you?
The meeting is over.
All of you, get out.
Get out, you morons.
Get out!
We are going.
Punks.
Hey!
You shouldn't stand there!
Get out of the way!
This is nuts!
Kangnam Family Office
From Gangnam to the world!
Min-jeong, a word?
- Sorry?
- It won't take long.
What is it?
Hold...
Hold this.
Sorry?
Hold like this.
When you are held like this,
bend it like this.
Bend it like this.
And...
Do it like what I just did.
What was that about?
You are so opinionated
but you say nothing to the boss.
It was so hard for me to get a job.
I didn't major in this field
but I got the editing certificate by
putting myself through academies.
I need more work experience.
You can free-lance.
I have no work experience.
Who would use me as a freelancer?
I like editing videos.
But if...
If people find out that I reported
my boss for sexual harassment,
I won't be able to get any jobs
in this field again.
I will be done.
I know what you are trying to say,
Hyun-seok.
Thanks.
But I will handle
my business on my own.
Yes, sir.
I will be there right away.
Both of us, now!
Hurry! Take a look at this!
That guy...
The guy I saw this morning.
What are you talking about?
Can you be quiet?
Let's take a look at this.
I need a backup.
Pause it there.
How can someone be that fast?
Could he be someone like
a jumper or an alien hybrid?
Huh? Hybrid?
Beings who teleport
or disappear out of nowhere
can be seen on YouTube videos.
That doesn't make any sense.
I am telling you.
What a shame.
That's right in front of our office.
We should've been the ones filming
something like that.
By the way, where have you been?
Toilet.
Did you go together?
No, separately.
If you have time to kill,
go out and film something like that!
Shall we shoot one like that?
You think? How?
I mean
we can put some special makeup
on a person
and scatter some fake blood.
How pathetic you just sounded.
You could screw the channel
fabricating content like that!
Let's do some thinking, shall we?
Please!
Yes, sir.
Play it back on!
Hyeon-cheol!
Yes, sir.
It's time to do rounds
with the landlady.
Get here quick. Okay?
Okay, I will be there soon.
What does it say?
Focus on your work.
Okay.
He is here again.
Sir!
Taekwondo Boy!
Water delivery!
Okay.
Yes, you mean the drone?
We have time. Yes.
Okay, thank you.
Good grief, this is so heavy.
My goodness.
What are you doing?
My boss isn't here today.
It looks like
your boss is over there.
No, he went out.
This is driving me nuts.
- Hey.
- Yes.
You know this is a tough job.
Each of
these gallons costs 9,000 won.
Three gallons per month
make 27,000 won.
That would make 108,000 won
for four months.
Do you know how much
I make selling this one gallon,
sweating a bucket?
I have already told my boss
so he will pay you soon.
- Soon?
- Yes.
- He will pay me soon?
I should get going taking
your word for it, then.
Sure.
You can go out this way.
This is the way out.
I envy your boss for having
such a nimble staff!
Bye, then.
Make sure he pays me soon.
Okay!
Bye!
Is he gone?
Go ahead and keep working.
Hey, stop it!
If they can't afford to drink water,
why order it?
They never pay and make me
work for it.
This doesn't bring much profit
to me.
Goodness.
It stinks!
It's always the poor
who never saves anything!
Can't you keep things straight?
My apologies, ma'am.
The cleaners have gone home
for the day.
If they have,
you should go around
and make things clean!
I am sorry, ma'am.
You guys are lowering
the value of this building!
It's always the poor who doesn't
have a sense of ownership.
Hey!
Hey.
You.
Where's your apology?
Look at you.
Young people these days.
I just asked where your apology is.
I am sorry, ma'am.
Good.
You should be sorry.
You know you are?
If you have been bad,
you should be told off.
Pick them up.
What's going on?
What's everyone doing
in my building?
What are you doing?
Go in and stop them!
Give me your radio.
- Block all the entrance doors!
- Sorry?
Block the entrance so no one can leave!
Yes, ma'am.
Lock all the doors!
What the hell is going on?
Help!
Hello!
Anybody here?
Please open the door!
Yes, there.
This is good.
If you do that...
That jerk...
Just like that.
Please open the door!
There are people in there!
What's going on?
There is...
There's a monster in this building!
What...
Why don't you call the police?
We can't do much for you about that.
No police!
The price of
this building will go down.
No police!
What kind of monster is it?
I don't know. What am I gonna do?
Wait.
It's that man.
That man.
That monster!
Oh, my goodness.
That's it.
Mr Kang!
If you guys catch that monster,
I will remit
from the rent you haven't paid.
What do you think?
- Are you sure?
- Of course!
- There are many witnesses here.
- Okay!
Boss,
you don't even know what
that monster is about.
We can just go out
and check ourselves.
This could be our chance to make our
popularity skyrocketed, right?
Yes.
Okay, we'll go and film it.
Let's go.
My goodness.
- Are you okay?
- What?
I am okay.
Wait.
Hurry.
Film it.
Film it now.
- Zombie!
- Now!
- Film it!
- Zombie!
Give it to me.
Go upstairs. Now!
Dae-yeong!
They are real zombies.
Let's call the police.
Give me your phone, boss.
I told you not to call the police!
- Ma'am!
- Please!
Let me check this first before
we call the police.
I filmed it good.
Is that important now?
- Let's call the cops first.
- Here!
Here's where the popular content is!
Just a moment.
Boss!
This is where your salaries are!
No!
- Give me the phone, boss!
- No way!
Hold on!
I don't want to become a zombie.
Dae-yeong!
I need to save him.
- No!
- Dae-yeong...
No, you can't!
Dae-yeong...
Did you throw
Dae-yeong
to the zombie to save your ass?
Hey, let go of me.
You are the one
who couldn't save Dae-yeong.
Why blame me?
Son of a bitch!
Knock it off!
Stop it
and let's call the police first.
No!
Please! Don't!
I put this building on
the market for sale!
I won't be able to sell
this building
if people know about this!
Do something!
No police!
Get it together.
You just saw how people changed.
That's not my fault.
How can something like
this happen in my building?
Ma'am.
Huh?
This can't be.
This building...
This building is my everything!
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
Run, Min-jeong!
Fuck, he became a zombie, too!
Help me!
What the fuck!
Let's go, Min-jeong.
Come!
Min-jeong, are you okay?
Min-jeong!
Hyun-seok.
Where are you?
What's going on, Min-jeong?
Did you have a nightmare?
It's nothing.
What do we do now?
As you said,
let's go to the office and call
someone outside of the building.
Then we should hide ourselves
at the office.
How will we get there?
We will be attacked by the zombies.
Don't worry.
I was a backup national athlete
in Taekwondo.
I will protect you.
You trust me, don't you?
I mean...
How are we going to get
to the office?
There's no way we can get there!
A way...
They are coming.
Okay, let's go.
Dae-yeong!
Hold like this.
When you are held like this,
bend it like this.
- Bend it like this.
- Do it like this.
Get it together, Dae-yeong!
Dae-yeong!
Wake up!
He is not the Dae-yeong you know
any more.
Let's go.
It's broken.
It's locked.
The land-line is broken, too.
Min-jeong.
Hey, dude.
Let's go again.
Is he dead?
I don't know.
Let's get out of here.
I think it's good to go.
Hold on.
What are we gonna do?
This way.
This way, Min-jeong.
I will lure the zombies.
You stay in here.
Don't go alone.
Don't worry.
I am was a backup national athlete.
I am totally screwed.
Hyun-seok.
Come on, bastards!
Hyun-seok, are you okay?
I am okay.
Huh!
Hyun-seok!
Hyun-seok, are you okay?
Did you get bitten?
I think so.
You go ahead, Min-jeong.
How can I leave you here?
No.
I will turn into a zombie soon.
You should go now.
If you go out now,
there may be a solution.
Come with me.
Don't be stubborn.
Go now.
I...
I wanted to go to
this concert with you.
Can I...
Can I hold you one last time?
I am good now.
You should go.
You should get going.
Go.
Den... Dentures...
Are you sure you were bitten?
I... I was...
That was...
Shall we go together?
Hurry up! Let's go.
" GANGNAM ZOMBIE "
Provided by Phat Huu
Modify by Blue-Bird™